{
  "questions": [
    {
      "date": "2025-10-27",
      "question": "Where are you hiding from your goobers? Dont  worry, none of your goobers have a phone to look at your website and find you. ",
      "answer": "I can't take any chances"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-27",
      "question": "what do you think of Dusty Douglas (aka Dusty Dubs), the animal voiceover guy",
      "answer": "Never heard of him"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-27",
      "question": "when did you start your career",
      "answer": "When I was born"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-27",
      "question": "Am i cool",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-27",
      "question": "why did people make 67:3",
      "answer": "Because it's a really cool ratio"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-27",
      "question": "who's your crush",
      "answer": "I have not crushed anyone yet"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-27",
      "question": "Are you related to raxdflipnote?",
      "answer": "Not by blood"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-27",
      "question": "when subscribing to your linktree i had to check a box labled \"I agree to my contact details being shared with zanelittle, who may contact me\" which feels so threatening.   I sure hope you dont have any Malicious Intent!!! :3",
      "answer": "As far as I know, I do not receive any details of the people who subscribe on Linktree"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-27",
      "question": "Should i persue my creative dreams in the arts of content creation, drawing and Music, or conform to societies expectations of being a wage slave forced to work on tedious menial labour to contribute to a comoany's greater impact",
      "answer": "The answer is in your heart"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-27",
      "question": "Do you eat eat you do eat you eat eat do eat you wonder you eat do eat you wonder you eat do do you wonder *insert laugh track*",
      "answer": "I do eat, I do wonder, I do not eat wonder"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-27",
      "question": "Do you like rats",
      "answer": "Yeah"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-27",
      "question": "Who is an animator you really look up to?",
      "answer": "GooberGrinder"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-27",
      "question": "What inspired you to write Inchworm? Did you just see an inchworm outside?",
      "answer": "I wanted to write a song in the style of Parry Gripp, so I needed a suitable critter"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-27",
      "question": "I found a way to farm clicks on the home page: hold your finger on the Champa icon, then swipe over it quickly, it gets loads of clicks but unfortunately doesn't spawn gooblers. Will you be patching this in any way?",
      "answer": "If I ever make clicks do anything more, probably"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-27",
      "question": "When I catch a Phantump in Pok√©mon Legends: Z-A, what do you think I should call it?",
      "answer": "Woody"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-27",
      "question": "what is your biggest fear",
      "answer": "Politics"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-26",
      "question": "what do you call a bird without eyes?",
      "answer": "Blind"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-26",
      "question": "Can you are is eat twenty seven cheeseburgers",
      "answer": "Given enough time, yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-26",
      "question": "Did you use to be 8 or 10 years old because of that dsi?",
      "answer": "The Dsi did not cause be to be 8 or 10 years old, no"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-26",
      "question": "Can we have more options for gooberbox",
      "answer": "Eventually"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-26",
      "question": "Why did the chicken cross the road",
      "answer": "Because it's what he had to do"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-26",
      "question": "are you gonna release lofty's workbench (remember that one time when you made music for him) as a song because that song is fire",
      "answer": "I gotta talk to Lofty about it but I think he'd be down!"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-25",
      "question": "Do the groovy specimens #3 Wunkner and #4 Dunkner related?",
      "answer": "I think so"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-25",
      "question": "Is this something like weird like c.ai or does this actually get answered by someone?",
      "answer": "I am actually answering these questions. I would never let AI write anything on my behalf. Especially c.ai, who have stolen a handful of my videos to use in their advertising."
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-25",
      "question": "Can I take Groovy Specimen #8 and make him my own character?",
      "answer": "Sure"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-25",
      "question": "Do you make videos?",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-25",
      "question": "Is GooberBox inspired by Incredibox?",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-25",
      "question": "Would you rather fight a single chicken every time you get on a car or fight a sword wielding orangutan every 6 months?",
      "answer": "I'd try to do a pacifist run whenever possible"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-25",
      "question": "You say youre music is royalty free,does that mean I can use your music for my animation? I'd be honored and I'll still credit you",
      "answer": "Yes!"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-25",
      "question": "what are you?",
      "answer": "A guy"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-25",
      "question": "do you have a web button I can add to my website? I love yours so much and want to share it",
      "answer": "Guess I gotta make one"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-25",
      "question": "Is this a ARG",
      "answer": "It's just an RG"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-25",
      "question": "do you ever go to voice chat in your discord server?",
      "answer": "No, but I might find a use for it some day"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-25",
      "question": "I'm a beginner pixel artist and I feel really inspired by your animations!! How do you do all this?? :D",
      "answer": "I use a Nintendo Dsi with Flipnote Studio"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-25",
      "question": "Its 4AM. do i go to sleep so i can be more productive tommorow, or just stay awake not being able to do anything for the rest of today?",
      "answer": "Sleep"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-25",
      "question": "why do you make music",
      "answer": "Because I have a lot of fun doing it"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-25",
      "question": "are you a little zany",
      "answer": "A lot more than a little"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-24",
      "question": "If you had to rank on a scale of 1 to 10, what would you rate?",
      "answer": "Derf"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-24",
      "question": "Whats the next groovy specimen to be done?",
      "answer": "Gotta head into the Goober fields and start searching"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-24",
      "question": "They had feelings. You made them. They were alive. You killed them short after short. They wanted out since wasdmovie 1. You didn't care And now THIS... is what's happening to you right now. Guess you ARE a coward and a murderer. Why didn't you let them out in the first place??? ",
      "answer": "If I let them out, I would not be able to make videos for you."
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-24",
      "question": "Why do you prefer Flipnote Studio than Flipnote Studio 3D, you have a 3DS",
      "answer": "I grew up with Flipnote Studio and I'm much more comfortable with it than 3D"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-24",
      "question": "Bro! Go to sleep!!! ",
      "answer": "I will eventually"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-24",
      "question": "Are you gonna make a playlist called: Zane's Little Archives? Where you show us your old flipnotes? Like the 2011 one you posted? ",
      "answer": "I probably should"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-24",
      "question": "help i got locked in your basement, could you let me out please?",
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-24",
      "question": "What is 9 plus ten",
      "answer": "9ten"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-24",
      "question": "I like you",
      "answer": "Thanks"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-24",
      "question": "Is Zane hyperactive or crazy?",
      "answer": "Both"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-24",
      "question": "where can I find the groovy specimens? ",
      "answer": "In the wild"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-24",
      "question": "will you make a msm like game?(and no i dont mean like drag and drop icons i mean with a shop mor islands and ill have all of the 20 groovy specimen the ones in gooberpedia and 10 new ones)",
      "answer": "GooberBox is like MSM but without the waiting"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-23",
      "question": "In \"The Champa Show In WALK\" how did champy got on fire? was it a camp fire or a fuel tank?",
      "answer": "Champa did not catch on fire"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-23",
      "question": "will you please change your pfp back like right now LIKE RIGHT NOW THIS VERY MOMENT AHHHHHHH THE VOICES WONT STOP",
      "answer": "It changes itself I can't do anything about it"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-23",
      "question": "Will you ever animate outside on Flipnote?",
      "answer": "I have animated on Flipnote in the outdoors a couple times"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-23",
      "question": "Was there a real-life event that inspired you to write Waste Our Time or was it just a spontaneous thing",
      "answer": "It was inspired by real events"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-23",
      "question": "What are some of Champa's favourite things to eat (besides the things we've seen him eat)",
      "answer": "Whatever is in his mouth at any given time becomes his favorite thing to eat"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-23",
      "question": "Why do Champa and Tank have maid outfits, and where did they get them",
      "answer": "I thought everyone had maid outfits"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-23",
      "question": "What is the hardest material that Champa's jaw can break through",
      "answer": "Diamon"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-23",
      "question": "Will there be a Cherub plush? If so then RIP my wallet lol",
      "answer": "Maybe some day!"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-23",
      "question": "HELLO XD nice website!!!!! Anyways I have ll question! How long in average does it takeaas to animate a short or a video:o",
      "answer": "A short Flipnote can take anywhere from 1-8 hours depending on how complex it is and how distracted I am"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-23",
      "question": "What is your opinion on the joe namath hallmark christmas ornament?",
      "answer": "It does not remind me of Christmas"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-23",
      "question": "How did Speedrick Faston become so fast?",
      "answer": "Gaming supplement drinks"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-23",
      "question": "Did You Make Groovy Specimens?",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-23",
      "question": "How fast can Speedrick Faston go?",
      "answer": "Supersonic (>768mph) in a vacuum. He would probably lose contact with the ground at about 170mph or so due to lift caused by air drag, but if he had a weight strapped to him, he would probably start eroding at about 500mph due to particles in the air sandblasting his skin. Assuming perfectly clean air, he'd probably make it close to 700mph before succumbing to 3rd degree burns."
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-23",
      "question": "If you could , what would you ?",
      "answer": "All of it"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-23",
      "question": "I actually have a few questions ",
      "answer": "Me too"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-23",
      "question": "Do you have any more of these for sale ",
      "answer": "I can sell you some of those if you want"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-23",
      "question": "When do you think you will? ",
      "answer": "Now"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-23",
      "question": "What‚Äôs your favourite candy? :-D",
      "answer": "I like the little peanut butter cups"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-23",
      "question": "My name is Zane Little ",
      "answer": "No I'm not"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-23",
      "question": "are the two cones/triangles at the top of your head in your animations horns or ears?     maybe PARTY HATS???",
      "answer": "They're horns, but they don't follow any of the rules"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-22",
      "question": "What games you got on your Nintendo ds?",
      "answer": "My Dsi XL has Art Academy in it right now"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-22",
      "question": "What are you New Year‚Äôs resolutions?",
      "answer": "I don't know yet"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-22",
      "question": "Whats your favorite thing to eat?",
      "answer": "Depends on the day"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-22",
      "question": "If you, what would you?",
      "answer": "I"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-22",
      "question": "i kinda like that Groovy specimen #6(peet), looks pretty cool. :)",
      "answer": "I think he's underrated"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-22",
      "question": "HOW ARE U GOOD AT SO MANNY THINGS!? Ts inspiring! ",
      "answer": "I keep getting obsessed with new things"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-22",
      "question": "hello funny internet feller, i got a question. How, the, fish, did you become the best person in the arts of music ive ever seen (and what do you use to make your music?) ok thanks!! :3 ",
      "answer": "It's up to you & FL Studio"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-22",
      "question": "Is Cherub Champa's girlfriend or are they just friends (I'm trying to not ask this in a weird way)",
      "answer": "We'll probably find out soon"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-22",
      "question": "Can you tell me the first letter of episode name for Champa Show 6? No prob if not, secrets n' that",
      "answer": "'C' - if I don't change it"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-22",
      "question": "Have you ever watched the Amazing Digital Circus? If not I think you would like it :)",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-22",
      "question": "Is Cherub aware that Champa has a wanted poster (as seen in 'Heat Wave')?",
      "answer": "Maybe"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-22",
      "question": "What is the RNG for a Goobler to spawn on the home page, also have you ever played Undertale or Deltarune",
      "answer": "1 in 10 - And I've played a little bit of Undertale"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-22",
      "question": "How long does it take you to make an animation?",
      "answer": "The long ones can take months"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-22",
      "question": "Should I say yes to the Halloween party next week?",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-21",
      "question": "how can i make chiptune songs like yours?",
      "answer": "Find a tool (like BeepBox!), and mess around with it until you make something cool"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-21",
      "question": "Did My Singing Monsters inspire your Groovy Specimens?",
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-21",
      "question": "How old are you",
      "answer": "Last 2 digits of the year most of the time"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-21",
      "question": "how did you get your name \"zane little\"",
      "answer": "It was given to me"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-21",
      "question": "Am I right to assume that Champa has a wanted poster in 'Heat Wave' because of property damage (The Champa Show: 'Sodey Pop'), as well as publix nuisance and accidental manslaughter x2 (The Champa Show: 'Walk')?",
      "answer": "Very likely"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-21",
      "question": "Is there gonna be a Inchworm Plush?",
      "answer": "Nope"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-20",
      "question": "How long did you own your DSi Xl?",
      "answer": "Since 2012"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-20",
      "question": "I really like those goober concert things you've made recently, are you planning on making more? They're sick.",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-20",
      "question": "Zane, do you like Toby Fox",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-20",
      "question": "do you play osu or audiosurf :)",
      "answer": "I used to play a lot of Audiosurf"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-20",
      "question": "will you make more speedrick faston videos",
      "answer": "Probably"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-20",
      "question": "Will the other person on the cover of Waste Our Time (I think I heard their name was Cherub) be in the next episode of the Champa Show? If you didn't plan on doing that then maybe the next one?",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-20",
      "question": "If you saw a cartoonishly big Mouse Trap would you eat the cheese?",
      "answer": "I would eat cheese next to a cartoonishly big mouse trap"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-20",
      "question": "What are gooblers on the website home page, also who is Zane Big",
      "answer": "They are gooblers - and we don't talk about Zane Big"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-20",
      "question": "Is there a lore reason I died 61.7 years ago?",
      "answer": "Possibly"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-20",
      "question": "Are you subbed to MrBeast? ",
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-19",
      "question": "which Animator vs Animation episode is your favourite?",
      "answer": "It's really hard to say. They keep getting better and better"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-19",
      "question": "schmorbly dorbly gobr dobr bmebbb",
      "answer": "Gar"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-19",
      "question": "do you use google on a daily basis",
      "answer": "Yeah"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-19",
      "question": "help me i dont know what im doing",
      "answer": "Stop doing everything and then you will know what you are doing"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-19",
      "question": "who is better at gaming champa or cherub",
      "answer": "I'm not sure either of them really play video games"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-19",
      "question": "can you pls make wasd 5",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-19",
      "question": "Hylics",
      "answer": "Is cool"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-19",
      "question": "When did you learn to code",
      "answer": "About 2014"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-19",
      "question": "what gave you the idea to start making flipnotes again",
      "answer": "I never stopped"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-19",
      "question": "Hi when is the next champa show and is the worst thing ever a series?",
      "answer": "Hopefully before November, and possibly"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "What do you do after making a video",
      "answer": "Start a new one"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "Do you like bananas?",
      "answer": "Sure"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "How did you start doing Flipnotes?",
      "answer": "I downloaded Flipnote in 2009 and started making animations forever"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "tips for coming up with random goobers on the spot?",
      "answer": "Just start drawing shapes and see what happens"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "how awesome do u think u are cuz i think very awesome what about you",
      "answer": "Pretty awesome I think"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "whats your favorite color",
      "answer": "I like blue"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "if you were a element on the periodic table what would you be",
      "answer": "Pb"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "Is Minecraft good",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "How do you combine audio in Flipnote Studio?",
      "answer": "Hold 'L' and tap 'Mix'"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "have you ever heard of zane little",
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "can i have your bed?",
      "answer": "Ok"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "why are you funny",
      "answer": "It's up to you"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "Do you know what pizza tower is?",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "do it jiggle",
      "answer": "Sometimes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "can you make it so groovy specimen number 54 is air",
      "answer": "Maybe"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "Favourite video game? Also least favourite, i wanna judge!!! :3",
      "answer": "Recently- Stardew Valley. I don't know least fav"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "how many gigabytes of raw flip notes do you have?",
      "answer": "Billions"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "what is champa's favorite movie?",
      "answer": "Madagascar 3"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "How old is champa?",
      "answer": "Not even he knows"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "Yes",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "Hello, Mr Little, this is Ethan at Otto Mechanic's Auto Mechanics. It appears that you forgot to pay for the headlight you got. Is there a problem?",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "Will you ever decide to be a butt head?",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "how do you get so swag?",
      "answer": "Lids"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "How does a piano",
      "answer": "Hammers and strings"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Google how to open jar with wet hand help",
      "answer": "Impossible"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "Can you make more groovy specimen concerts",
      "answer": "There will be many"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "Ever been to germany? ",
      "answer": "Perhaps some day"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "What's your opinion on the colour ourple (not purple)",
      "answer": "good"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-18",
      "question": "do you have flipnote studio on your new 2ds XL? ",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "Could you do a Mummy Joe collab?",
      "answer": "If he wants"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "What inspired Bobotron?",
      "answer": "Bobotron"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "What do you do when you're Bored?",
      "answer": "work on Drawmegle"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "dude, have you EVER TRIED coloring your groovy specimens/gooberpedia entries? I suggest you to do it!",
      "answer": "The Flipnote ones can only be black, white, blue, or red. But more colors are being explored in the new stuff."
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "do you like pizza and garlic butter",
      "answer": "yeah"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "if you were a flavor of cake what would it be",
      "answer": "water flavor"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "what is 1+1 is it fish or 2 tell me",
      "answer": "I don't know"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "Can you please draw a dragon? I love dragons!",
      "answer": "I will probably draw a dragon some day"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "we need all groovy specimen looped 10 hours PLEASE PLEASE PLEASEEEE IM BEGGING YOU AAAAAAaAAAA",
      "answer": "just play it on loop for 10 hours"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "How many eggs can you fit in your mouth before you stop breathing?",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "Will larrys journey continue?",
      "answer": "Probably"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "do you knoweth of homestuck?",
      "answer": "yesth"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "How old is Tank?",
      "answer": "Nobody knows"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "are You an alien with a human body?",
      "answer": "I don't know"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "Which animation that you'v made so far is your favorite/most proud of?",
      "answer": "The newest one"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Favorite genre of music + artists",
      "answer": "Probably digital fusion"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "How do I get more then two sounds on gooberbox",
      "answer": "Don't use iPhone"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "why is gang so good at drawing on a ds",
      "answer": "Gang probably practiced a lot"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "What is your upcoming game? ",
      "answer": "Many"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "Baked beans?",
      "answer": "Sure"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "Are oranges orange because orange is orange or is the color orange because oranges are orange",
      "answer": "The fruit came first"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "is there gonna be more concerts for the other groovy specimens?",
      "answer": "Absolutely"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "Are you happy about your existence? ",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "How many cool points do you have?",
      "answer": "At least 6"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "opinion on 2+2?",
      "answer": "Better than 1+1"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "What is Speedrick Faston's top speed so far?",
      "answer": "Immeasurable"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "What do you do when random 3am motivation hits you?",
      "answer": "Sleep"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "How did you get you ds?",
      "answer": "I bought most of them"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "What‚Äôs the hardest thing you‚Äôve had to overcome when making this website.",
      "answer": "Making it useful probably"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "waffle or pancake",
      "answer": "Waffle"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "do you watch hazbin hotel or helluva boss?",
      "answer": "Nope"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "Why do you do what you do? What motivates you to keep going?",
      "answer": "I just love it, and that's what keeps me going!"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "Do you like Dr pepper?",
      "answer": "Yea it's pretty good"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "how many days until bag of chips vol.4?",
      "answer": "I dunno"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-17",
      "question": "Are you thinking about making an msm island about your groovy specimens?",
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Best flavor of cheese?",
      "answer": "Yellow"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Will you ever make a sad backstory of how you found Tank?",
      "answer": "Maybe some day"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "what is a goober",
      "answer": "Anything"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Did you grow up with the DSi XL you animate a lot on?",
      "answer": "I started with a normal DSi in 2009, then got the XL in 2012"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Are you gonna fix groovy specimen 6",
      "answer": "Probably"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Is a pound of steel heavier then a pound of feathers?",
      "answer": "if we're talking British Pounds, yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "There will gooberbox v2?",
      "answer": "eventually"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "favorite rock band?? (if you have one)",
      "answer": "Stone Jones and Sedimentary Sanders"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Right on ",
      "answer": "Left off"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "How long have you been using YouTube for?",
      "answer": "Almost 20 years"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Who Is The Most insane video?",
      "answer": "I do not know any videos personally"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Is animating your favorite thing?",
      "answer": "one of them"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "what do you think of antidisestablishmentarianism?",
      "answer": "it's one of the longer words"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Who‚Äôs the girl on the cover of Waste Our Time?",
      "answer": "Cherub"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "does gribford have turophobia ",
      "answer": "no"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Is a hot dog a sandwich or a taco",
      "answer": "it's a living breathing thing"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Is gooberpedia dead or are there gonna be more",
      "answer": "it's only getting started"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "What's your zodiac sign?",
      "answer": "chunk meat"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "do you... uuh.... I forgot...",
      "answer": "yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Why is there a moose outside my house",
      "answer": "that's no moose"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "why do we have the same name",
      "answer": "because we were both given the same name"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "why are you",
      "answer": "cuz"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Will you Survive from your goobers in wasdmovie? How? ",
      "answer": "hiding"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "zane, do you like owls ü¶â ",
      "answer": "yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "When are you gonna add other stuff to gooberbox?",
      "answer": "I plan to, but don't know when"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "What are your opinions on hamsters?",
      "answer": "I think they're pretty funny"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "why are you so good at making flipnotes",
      "answer": "cup o' joe in the morning"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "What was your favorite groovy specimen that you made so far?",
      "answer": "I like Bloktorb"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Do you have plans to collab with a lot of YouTubers or am I stupid and you've already collabed with one?",
      "answer": "I've collabed with several"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Do you worship cheese?",
      "answer": "I worship grater things"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "do you like waffles",
      "answer": "yeah we like waffles"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "insert cash or select payment type",
      "answer": "doubloons"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Your existence implies the existence of a zane big,whats your take on this?",
      "answer": "We do not talk about zane big..."
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "send music recs., favorite tracks/genres/artists",
      "answer": "I like digital fusion stuff, but also anything interesting. Nelward, Jett Mance, Igorrr, Anomalie, Snarky Puppy to name a few"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "make a groovy sound",
      "answer": "Buh"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "What's an animal you know about (basic stuff like name and appearance) that no one else seems to know about?",
      "answer": "Goobulationoidotronator"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "How did you make your mascot (Champa)",
      "answer": "Adding features to a stick figure over the course of years"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "you know how to program ?? favorite language??",
      "answer": "I don't know anything"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "What do you do on off days to make yourself feel better, if you have them? Also I LOVE your videos, keep it up man <3",
      "answer": "Spending time with loved ones - and making stuff"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "red pill or blue pill",
      "answer": "Vitamin C pill"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "how many groovy specimens are you gonna make?",
      "answer": "hundreds"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "When did you create your very first Flipnote?",
      "answer": "2009"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "How does this qna work",
      "answer": "duct tape"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "What do you think of youtube",
      "answer": "It's mostly good"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "are you secretly an alien?",
      "answer": "If I tell you it won't come true"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Do you actually eat glass",
      "answer": "maybe"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Why do you like making crazy stuff? ",
      "answer": "cuz I think it's funny"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Would you rather have unlimited bacon but no games, or games (unlimited games), but no games?",
      "answer": "no"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Can you describe the process you go through for the sound design part of your vids? I‚Äôm especially curious about the groovy specimens",
      "answer": "I post a lot of videos about that"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Will you ever answer this specific question?",
      "answer": "possibly"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "what do you do when the haters dab back!??!",
      "answer": "kill them"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Of all the songs you've done, which is your favorite?",
      "answer": "the newest one"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "What's a video idea you thought of but scrapped? (If any.)",
      "answer": "A lot, but I might come back to them someday"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Why do they call it oven when you of in the cold food of out hot eat the food?",
      "answer": "cuz you of in first"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Is this a question?",
      "answer": "yes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Do you live for a living?",
      "answer": "sometimes"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Zane, How did you use animation?",
      "answer": "I used it to animate"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "8 x 8.",
      "answer": "at least 6"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Zane are you little",
      "answer": "depends"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "what do you do with your free time?? do you animate more or idk...sleep???",
      "answer": "Animation, music, gamedev"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Do you like to use Flipnote?",
      "answer": "I love to use Flipnote"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Is cheese the meaning of life",
      "answer": "Only if you believe it is"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "What‚Äôs your opinion about raxdflipnote?",
      "answer": "I think he rax"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Do you ever think you'll make a fully fledged game, or just fun little stuff? (both are completely valid of course!!!)",
      "answer": "I would love to make a game as soon as I can buy the time"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "How did you meet Tomska?",
      "answer": "fate"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Zaneth why do you like glass so much?",
      "answer": "it's funny"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "how long does it typically take to make a flip ote",
      "answer": "It can take anywhere from an hour to all day"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "What was youre first flipnote you ever Made?",
      "answer": "A really cool one"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "When?",
      "answer": "Now"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Ya like jazz?",
      "answer": "I love it"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Crunchy peanut butter or smooth peanut butter?",
      "answer": "Depends on the day"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "What inspired you to make animations?",
      "answer": "Discovering Flipnote"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-16",
      "question": "Have you played any Klonoa or Bomberman game",
      "answer": "I've played some Bomberman but it's been a while"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-15",
      "question": "zane can you make more of the groovy specemen",
      "answer": "yea"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-15",
      "question": "Why do you smell so bad?",
      "answer": "cuz"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-15",
      "question": "I like your vids!",
      "answer": "THANX"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-15",
      "question": "what is patreon",
      "answer": "It's where you can give me money"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-15",
      "question": "when did you buy flipnote studio",
      "answer": "I downloaded it in 2009"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-15",
      "question": "who are u",
      "answer": "zane"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-15",
      "question": "so how much do you make flipnote animations?",
      "answer": "all the time"
    },
    {
      "date": "2025-10-15",
      "question": "Hello",
      "answer": "World"
    }
  ]
}